LUCAS FELICIANO

BACKEND DEVELOPER





Portfólio



/LucasFeliciano02



(41) 9 8736-9451



lucas.feliciano02@outlook.com

Curitiba, PR, Brasil

PERFIL

I've been working with open source projects for the past two years in order to gain experience to continue my career transition to software development with a focus on the backend.

I have courage, a lot of curiosity and passion to learn more and more so that I can grow within the company and continue to deliver a lot of value and results together to the group.

SKILLS

- Python
- Django MVT
- Git & GitHub
- MySQL
- SQLite
- Rest Api Flask Api and FastApi
- Html | css | Js | Bootstrap
- Gui Tkinter
- Microsoft Office
- English (intermediary)

EXPERIENCE

OPEN SOURCE PROJECTS

My skills are applied to several other projects that are on my github with more detailed descriptions.

2021 - Present

- Project Email sending web with python, django, html and css; (Project Link)
- **Project** Web for patient management by a nutritionist made in Django, python, bootstrap, sqlite and that uses the sha256 token as validation for registration; (Project Link)
- **Project** Web application for hiring freelancers made in Django, python, html, css, boostrap; (Project Link)
- **Project** Office form desktop app that integrates with a sqlite database with CRUD functions; (Project Link)
- Project Desktop currency converter app that uses an API that contains quotes from multiple currencies. (Project Link)

IBGE - Brazilian Institute of Geography and Statistics

RESEARCH AND MAPPING AGENT

2022 - present

• I am a Public Servant of the IBGE, I work in a Governmental Public Administration in the sector of survey and production of price indices for the calculation of state and national inflation, through the collection of the price of products and services of companies.

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Universidade Positivo

2022 - Present

ANALYSIS AND SYSTEMS DEVELOPMENT

Unicesumar

2021 - 2022